Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
- Box: 52, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Public Service Alliance of Canada: Group: Programme Administration (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Alliance de la Fonction publique du Canada: Groupe: Administration des program, 1975; Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Box: 52, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Public Alliance of Canada., 1985; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Public Alliance of Canada., 1985; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Public Alliance of Canada., 1988; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Constitution of the Public Alliance of Canada., 1988; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Constitution of the Public Alliance of Canada, 1976; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
    Notes: photocopy
- Box: 52, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Public Alliance of Canada, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Public Alliance of Canada, 1976; Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Constitution and regulations of the Public Service Alliance of Canada, 1988; Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Notes: Working copy
  - Item 4: Constitution and regulations of the Public Service Alliance of Canada, 1988; Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Box: 52, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Facts about Group Insurance Value and Protection, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Public Service Alliance of Canada, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Weekly Newsletter, 1977; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Box: 52, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Forger notre unite dans un syndicalisme de masse, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
    Author: Centrale de l'enseignement du Quebec. President.
    Language: French.
- Box: 52, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Fronts communs, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
    Author: Robert Gaulin
  - Item 2: Publications de la Centrale liste selective, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
    Author: Centrale de l'enseignement du Quebec.
  - Item 3: Decret relatif a l'industrie de la construction dans la province de Quebec, 1977; Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
    Author: Office de la construction du Quebec
  - Item 4: Statutes and by-laws, 1976; Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Collective agreement consequent on the entente concluded between, 1975; Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Box: 52, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Profil 76-78, Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Prospectus: L'education syndicale de base a la CEQ, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Structures de la CEQ, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Front Common Secteur Public, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Bulletin no. 3
  - Item 5: Front Common Secteur Public, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Bulletin no. 4
  - Item 6: Front Common Secteur Public, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Bulletin no. 2
  - Item 7: Front Common Secteur Public, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Bulletin no. 6
  - Item 8: La Situation, La CEQ en negociation - Bilan 5, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Les Enjeux d'un livre orange, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Innover au passe, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Labour Journalists' Report, 1983; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Author: Labour Canada
  - Item 12: Les Colleges a l'ancre, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Dossier 1
  - Item 13: Les Colleges a l'ancre, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Dossier 2
  - Item 14: Les Colleges a l'ancre, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Dossier 3
  - Item 15: Les Colleges a l'ancre, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Dossier 4
  - Item 16: Les Colleges a l'ancre, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Dossier 5
- Box: 52, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Dix ans de pratiques syndicales: CEQ, 1970-1980, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
    Author: Louise Clermont-Laliberte
  - Item 2: L'exercice de la responsabilite syndicale, 1983; Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: La dimension politique de nos pratiques syndicales, 1983; Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Notre organisation democratique, 1983; Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Notre organisation democratique, 1983; Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
    Author: Centrale de l'enseignement du Quebec
  - Item 6: Les delegues syndicaux, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Decisions des Congres, 1967-1980 Index, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Definir nos Pratiques Syndicales, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Today at school, let's talk about miners, 1982; Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Box: 52, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Publications de la Centrale, 1989; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Batir Notre Avenir, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Origine et developpement de la CEQ, 1977; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
    Notes: Novembre 1977
  - Item 4: Batir Notre Avenir, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Origine et developpement de la CEQ, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
    Notes: Fevrier 1981
  - Item 6: Convention collective, grief et arbitrage, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Le Syndicat, cellule de base, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Vie et pratiques syndicales, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Relations et solidarite internationales, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Prendre une decision democratique, 1983; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
    Notes: Juin 1983
  - Item 11: Mouvements, 1983; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Box: 52, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Index, Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
    Author: Syndicat des fonctionnaires provinciaux du Quebec
  - Item 2: Provisions constituting collective agreements between of the one part, the Gouvernement du Quebec"Civil Servants" Unit, 1983- 1985 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Provisions constituting collective agreements between of the one part, the Gouvernement du Quebec"Workers" Unit, 1983-1985 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Police C.U.M.: 84 Rapport Annuel, 1976; Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
    Author: Association de Bienfaisance et de Retraite de la Police de Montreal
  - Item 5: Police C.U.M.: 84 Rapport Annuel, 1976; Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Box: 52, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Declaration de principes statuts le code des regles de procedure, 1987; Publication (Box 52, Folder 13)
    Author: Syndicat des Fonctionnaires Provinciaux du Quebec
  - Item 2: Declaration de principes statuts le code des regles de procedure, 1987; Publication (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Statuts, 1985; Publication (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Statuts: declaration de principes, 1987; Publication (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Box: 52, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Declaration de Principes, 1981; Publication (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Convention collective de travail 78-82: entre le Gouvernement du Quebec et le Syndicat des fonctionnaires provinciaux du Quebec, Unite: Fonctionnaires, 1980; Publication (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Convention collective de travail 1975-1978 entre le Gouvernement du Quebec et le Syndicat des fonctionnaires provinciaux du Quebec, Unite ouvriers., 1976; Publication (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Convention collective de travail 1975-1978 entre le Gouvernement du Quebec et le Syndicat des fonctionnaires provinciaux du Quebec, Unite fonctionnaires., Publication (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Box: 53, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Convention collective de travail 1975-1978 entre le Gouvernement du Quebec et le Syndicat des fonctionnaires provinciaux du Quebec, Unite fonctionnaires., Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Reglements reglements, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Declaration de principes, 1972; Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Convention collective de travail 1976-1979, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Convention collective de travail: 78-82.Ouvriers, 1978-1982 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Box: 53, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Statuts et code des regles de procedure, 1989; Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: SFPQ. Syndicat des fonctionnaires provinciaux du Quebec, 1985; Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Statuts et code des regles de procedure, 1989; Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Moi! Et mon syndicat?, 1977; Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Mon travail et mes droits, 1977; Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Box: 53, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Reglements Syndicat des Fonctionnaires Provinciaux de Quebec Inc., Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Liste des reglements de la commission de la fonction publique concernant, 1976; Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Reglement de la commission de la fonction publique, Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Entente between on one part the Quebec Association of Protestant School Boards on behalf of the School Boards and Regional Boards for Protestants of Quebec and the Minister of Education, and the Provincial Association of Protestant Teachers on behalf of t, 1977; Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Author: Quebec Association of Protestant School Boards
- Box: 53, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Collective agreement between the M.U.C. Security Council (hereinafter called "the Employer") and the Montreal Urban Community Policemen's Brotherhood Inc. (hereinafter called "the Brotherhood") for the period 1st January 1974 to 31st December 1974, Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Author: Montreal Urban Community Policemen's Brotherhood Inc.
    Notes: annual
  - Item 2: Collective agreement between the M.U.C. Security Council (hereinafter called "the Employer") and the Montreal Urban Community Policemen's Brotherhood Inc. (hereinafter called "the Brotherhood") for the period 1st January 1974 to 31st December 1974, Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Box: 53, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Montreal Urban Community Policemen's Brotherhood Inc., 1976; Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Montreal Urban Community Policemen's Brotherhood Inc., 1976; Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Fraternite des policiers de la communaute urbaine de Montreal Inc., 1976; Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Box: 53, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Saskatchewan Federation of Labour: as amended to and including the 21st Annual Convention, October 28, 29, 30, 1976, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
    Author: Saskatchewan Federation of Labour
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Saskatchewan Federation of Labour: as amended to and including the 21st Annual Convention, October 28, 29, 30, 1976, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Saskatchewan Federation of Labour: as amended to and including the 32nd Annual Convention, October 21, 22, 23, 1987, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Constitution of the Saskatchewan Federation of Labour: as amended to and including the 32nd Annual Convention, October 21, 22, 23, 1987, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Constitution of the Saskatchewan Federation of Labour: as amended to and including the 27th Annual Convention, October 20, 21, 22, 23, 1985, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Constitution of the Saskatchewan Federation of Labour: as amended to and including the 27th Annual Convention, October 20, 21, 22, 23, 1985, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Constitution of the Saskatchewan Federation of Labour: as amended to and including the 34th Annual Convention, November 1-3, 1989, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Constitution of the Saskatchewan Federation of Labour: as amended to and including the 27th Annual Convention, October 20, 21, 22, 23, 1982, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Box: 53, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Seafarers' International Union of Canada: affiliated with the Seafarers' International Union of North America, American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, Canadian Labor Congress: Effective December 1976, Publication (Box 53, Folder 7)
    Author: Seafarers' International Union of Canada
  - Item 2: Constitution du Syndicat International des Marins Canadiens, 1976; Publication (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Box: 53, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Study of the impact of potential free trade in textiles and clothing between Canada and the United States: final report / Textile and Clothing Board = Etude des consequences economiques d'un libre- echange eventuel des produits du textile et du ve^t, 1984; Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Author: Canada. Textile and Clothing Board.
- Box: 53, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Labour conditions in the men's clothing industry, 1935; Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)
    Author: F.R. Scott
- Box: 53, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: British Columbia Federation of Labour submission to the Select Standing Committee of the Provincial Legislature on Mines and Railways in the Matter of Surface Mining., 1969; Publication (Box 53, Folder 10)
    Author: British Columbia Federation of Labour (C.L.C.)
  - Item 2: Seminars for workers, 1970-1972, Publication (Box 53, Folder 10)
    Author: Caribbean Congress of Labour; Friedrich-Ebert-Stiftung
  - Item 3: Inflation, the millstone around the worker's neck, 1977; Publication (Box 53, Folder 10)
    Author: George I. Brizan
  - Item 4: This is who we arethe Federation: Voice of 200,000 British Columbians, Publication (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Box: 53, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: National Seminar on Employment, Colombo, July 24th-July 29th, 1978, Publication (Box 53, Folder 11)
    Author: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions; Ceylon Workers' Congress
- Box: 53, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Estructura de las organizaciones sindicales, 198-; Publication (Box 53, Folder 12)
    Author: Patricio Castro
- Box: 53, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: This is where we standon Housing., Publication (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 53, Folder 13)
    Notes: Aprl 2nd, 1979.
  - Item 3: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: News from the B.C Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 53, Folder 13)
    Notes: ecember 15, 1978.
  - Item 5: Informe del Director general - Instituto Colombiano de Seguros Sociales, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    Author: Instituto Colombiano de Seguros Sociales
- Box: 53, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Health and Safety in the Workplace, 1983; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1982; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
    Notes: January 27, 1982.
  - Item 3: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1983; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
    Notes: March 1, 1983.
  - Item 4: Dr. Gordon Atherley, 1982; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Dr. Gordon Atherley, 1982; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Health and Safety in the Workplace in the 1980s' Conference, 1983; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Health and Safety in the Workplace, 1983; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: 'Health and Safety in the Workplace in the 1980s' Conference, 1983; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Resolutions submitted by the B.C. Federation of Labour to the C.L.C. Executive, June 16, 1981, Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: 4a. Convencion Colectiva de Trabajo, Celebrada entre Sitradique y la CIA. Bananera de Costa Rica, 1977; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
    Author: Sindicato de Trabajadores de la Division de Quepos
  - Item 13: 4a. Convencion Colectiva de Trabajo, Celebrada entre Sitradique y la CIA. Bananera de Costa Rica, 1977; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: 4a. Convencion Colectiva de Trabajo, Celebrada entre Sitradique y la CIA. Bananera de Costa Rica, 1977; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: 4a. Convencion Colectiva de Trabajo, Celebrada entre Sitradique y la CIA. Bananera de Costa Rica, 1977; Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Box: 53, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1984; Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1984; Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    Notes: January 17, 1984.
  - Item 3: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1984-1987 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    Notes: press releases June 6, 1984-November 18, 1987
  - Item 4: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1988; Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    Notes: '88 Convention Memo
  - Item 5: AFL-CIO Noticiero del Movimiento Sindical Libre, 1980; Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.35:no.9 (1980:Dec.)
- Box: 53, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Correspondence: To All Affiliated and Friendly Organisations, 1964; Publication (Box 53, Folder 16)
    Author: Trade Unions International of Metal and Engineering Industries
  - Item 2: Correspondence: Brothers, 1960; Publication (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Correspondence: Brothers, 1960; Publication (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: One million Italian Metal and Engineering Workers take action, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: The development of air transport and its repercussions on the workers, 1961; Publication (Box 53, Folder 16)
    Author: Trades Unions International of Transport, Port and Fishery Workers
- Box: 53, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Communique, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
    Author: Trade Union International of Transport, Port and Fishery Workers
  - Item 2: Press Communique, 1961; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Press Communique, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Documents adopted by the Third International Trade Conference -- Circular No. 65, 1961; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Solidarity with the Workers and People of Spain -- Circular No. 16, 1963; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Solidarity with the workers of South Africa -- Circular No. 15, 1963; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Solidarity with the Drivers' Union o fNicaragua -- Circular No. 14, 1963; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: To affiliated organisations -- Circular No. 48, 1960; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Press Communique, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Resolution on the 7th Session of the Coal Mines Committee, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
    Author: Administrative Committee of the Miners' Trade Unions International
  - Item 11: Resolution on the VIIth World Festival of Youth and Students for Peace and Friendship, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: To All Mine Workers and their Trade Unions throughout the world for the Third International Miners Conference, 1958; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 13: Resolution 1, 1958; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 14: General Resolution, 1958; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 15: Resolution on Marcinelle, 1958; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 16: Resolution on the Committees proposed for the Third International Miners' Conference at Katowice, 1958; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 17: General Resolution, 1958; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 18: Resolution on the holding of the Third International Miners' Conference at Katowice, 1958; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 19: Resolution on the draft agenda for the Third International, 1958; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 20: Resolution on the activities of the Miners' Trade Unions International, 1958; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 21: Dear Brothers: We enclose, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
    Author: Miners' Trade Unions International (Trade Department of the WFTU)
    Notes: bundled
  - Item 22: General Resolution - The 3rd International Miners' Conference, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 23: Resolution on the 2nd Item on the Agenda, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 24: Resolution on health and safety in mines and on social security, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 25: Resolution on the Auditors' report, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 26: Resolution on the European Coal and Steel Community and the Common Market, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 27: Letter from the International Conference of Miners to the Foreign Ministers', Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 28: Letter to the Director General of the International Labour Office, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 29: Letter to the Secretary General of the United Nationas Organisation, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 30: Letter on Unity and Action to the Secretary-Treasurer o the Miners' International, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 31: Letter on Unity and Action to the International Federation of Christian Miners' Unions, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 32: Statement on Spain, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 33: Open Letter from the Third International Miners' Conference, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 34: Letter to American Miners, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 35: Resolution on the situation in Vietnam, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 36: Resolution calling for the release of Aissat IDIR and his colleagues and for peace in Algeria, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 37: Message to the Youth, gathered in Vienna, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 38: Resolution on the situation in Korea, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 39: Recommendations of the Press and Propaganda Committee, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 40: Report of the Credentials Committee, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 41: Appeal to the Miners of the World, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 42: Motion calling for the release of Manolis Glezos, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 43: Protest by the Miners' Trade Unions International against the shameful verdict on Marcinelle, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 44: General Resolution, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 45: Resolution on the 2nd Item on the Agenda, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 46: Resolution on health and safety in mines and on social security, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 47: Resolution on the Auditors' report, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 48: Resolution on the European Coal and Steel Community and the Common Market, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 49: Letter from the International Conference of Miners to the Foreign Ministers' in Geneva, 1959; Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)